So, hello everyone in this video, we are going to just write some functions related to
validating credentials, okay.
So for that first which we are going to do is import toast is from react host.
So react host, we are going to just import this toast package from react host and I have
copied one function for this variegate credential.
So I am just going to paste here and I am going to explain why it is used like for this
const validate credentials if user name is not present, okay.
In that case we are just returning that toast.error like from this toast package full
name is required.
Similarly for email we are going to return as toast.error email is required and for this
email we have a particular format like suppose asmocodes at the rate of gmail.com, okay.
So for that purpose I have just pasted this pattern here in order to test whether the email
format is correct or not and same thing for the password like if the password is not present
then we are going to just return the toast.error password is required.
Similarly if the password is not length is smaller than 6 in that case we are just returning
the toast.error password must be at least 6 characters long.
So we are just going to use this validate credentials function.
So what we are actually going to do is suppose like for example we have to copy this one
and paste it here.
There is a lot of sound that is coming from outside that is why I have to cut the video.
So now after this we are just going to just use this function okay.
So validate credentials copy this one and we are going to just use it here and we are going
to write also the conditions we can directly use it like this okay.
So if the validate credentials function is returning true like it is returning true then
in that case we are just going to take this that sign of function.
So let us do one thing here what we actually can do is we can just take our sign of function
from the author store so const let's destructure it so sign of equals to author store.
So we are just going to take up this sign of function we are going to just re destructure
it from this author store and we are just going to return this sign up and with that we
are going to take whatever there is it in like username and email and password okay.
So control let's save so we can just import it I think it is not defined so import author
store from dash okay where is the author store actually I think it is in the okay store
folder so wait a second so dot dot slash store slash author store.
So we can save it now we can test this one so what we actually going to do that in the
terminal let's go to the front end folder CD front end and NPM run dev let's start this
one so it's going to start up so let's navigate to this site.
Let's go to the I guess it was sign up is right so we have this so what we can do is
SMO underscore okay asthma courts and we'll have this asthma courts at the rate of gmail.com
and we are just going to take whatever the password is for instance I'm going to use my
password here and let's hit the sign up okay sign up is failed please try again I think
there's some issue with like we haven't started the backend but as you can see that this
toast package is working right so there's a error connection issue with local host 5000
so that means that it is not working like the backend is not running up but as you can
see we will just when you just run the backend it will automatically so the success page okay
So, you can try on this, we will meet in the next video.